What happened, Papa?   The
doctor is doing the checkup right now.  I will tell you now
what to do.
Okay,
sit for a while.  Have some patience.
Ok.   Things are
going as if it is about to be seized.
Yes,
we
are fine.  Let's see what the doctor says.
Ok.   Is that a
feeding gown for lats.
What?
Where to get it from?
Me.   Bring it.  Then go.
Bhabhi is neither going to have a baby nor does she
need a feeding gown.
So let's take it.
Chained ones in front.
What is there to ask?  Go and bring it in.   Let us go.
Come on child, you go, you go
with them, you go, no no,
why is it my work,
what is this, mummy,
this is the child's dupatta, let's
say it,
yes, by the way, don't keep it like this on the child,
which color is cute, this one,
this one looks more fresh, this one,
this one, guys,
you can guess whether a baby boy will be born in our house
or a baby girl, we are
buying it accordingly, we chose blue because
its color was looking very fresh, there are
other colors here too, but this one is the
cutest among these.   I do
n't think this is its color.  What do you
say?  Doraemon Color.
Yes Doraemon Doraemon
look at these feeding gowns, they are like this.
Show him that there is no zip here.
We are right.   I
need cotton ones.   The
cotton ones are cool.  Comfortable.  Look,
we have bought these two gowns because these colours will
suit Bhabhi and will also do the same and will
not spoil anything.  If there is a stain, it will not be visible.
And this cotton is also very comfortable.  This is
mommy, isn't it? She is also buying a small cap
for the baby. This cute cap has to be
worn like this immediately after the baby is born.
Look, hot
samosas are being served here and he has come behind the
samosas. He is very hungry but he is
not going to eat samosas.
Yes, I could not refuse him for that.
Now we will do this more often, we will do
this way, guys,
look, we have come home and while coming we have
brought pani puri for mommy. Here
aunty, eat pani puri.   Thank
you.
Welcome.
And the rest is to bring the luggage in the car.
Look at these hot samosas and slippers.
Look, everyone is sitting and eating.  And aunty has
just become a pani puri seller here.  Now
aunty will feed everyone.
Will you eat pani puri?
No.
Call your sister-in-law.
We have already eaten.
Yes.  You guys came back after eating from there.
Yes, we are smarter.   I
ate from there and came back.  This uncle doing self service.
So guys, we have just taken out all the stuff.
Everyone had their breakfast and water.
Look, these two are left at the end for breakfast,
so have breakfast,
everyone here, ma'am,
yes, we have to keep them separately,
ma'am's stuff is different,
everyone is sitting in a group,
what is there to take out the stuff here,
how much did I bring it,
yes, I don't have a pudding to make che,
no, remember for ginger, I have to grind
garlic, I have to grind ginger, I don't have to grind it in the mixer, so do it in that, nice, wow, it's good, isn't it cool, it's cool, is it ...
And today I did a full body workout
and my condition became very bad, so I came and went
straight to sleep and now when I woke up in the evening, this
grandmother is tying a black thread for me,
Papa, do you want to tie a black thread?
Yes.   Come.
No, I am not tying it.  I
already have this colorful one.
I had that too but tie it up.  You will
also be affected by evil eye.  Are you going to the gym now?
No, this is fine for me.
Hey, tie it up, friend.
Papa, do you ever tie me up so much?
Yes, said grandmother.   Does
n't fly.
What is happening here?   When
Aadi comes from Palm, he does not perform Aarti of small children.  They
come to him.  If you speak in Marathi,
he comes.
Why do you do that?  And today he also makes me wear a black thread.
So I have worn it too.  Look at this.
Why did you install so many lamps?  But
today all the lamps in the house are
especially worshipped.
Does Kirti live with you
in the village?
No.   Does
n't it happen?  Why don't you do good work
in the village?  [laughter]
That doesn't happen.
This does not happen.
Well, that doesn't happen.   There is
no worship.
Deep puja is performed only once a year.
On Diwali.
Come on, tell me and do it quickly.
Look, today aunty's first puja is this, she is
doing it in our house and is
teaching it how to do it, what should I tell the
lamp to keep shining like this in our house
and there should be happiness and peace, everything should keep
shining like this, there should be happiness and peace in our house
and everything should keep
shining like a lamp,
yes
our badge has also come,
everyone is sitting to see it, we will sit here,
yes, sitting here near God,
aunty is applying the tilak.  Come here and
sit next to sister.  Right now aunty is giving
Tipu the vaccination.  Then he will
come.  Whatever these flour lamps become, this one will
just
give the blessings of my aunt [music] [music]
You are also mother's child, right?  Come and sit.
[laughter] You look good.
You look very good after getting the vaccine.  Isn't it guys?
Tell me by commenting.  Show me, show me here.
Looks very beautiful.  [Music]
Look guys, it's mama's turn now.  Aunty and mother are
wearing the same saree.  Twinning
today.
Quickly.  Oh my God [laughs] guys
we have just gone out
because I had to buy protein powder
and momos for the family members,
they all feel like eating momos so we have gone
out and I have to buy phone
stickers too, we will take everything
and Kirti has also come along, hi Kirti, we will
feed Kirti also something delicious, what do you want to
eat outside, think about it and tell me, I will
think about it and tell you,
I want to
eat Dabeli,
okay, I have Dabeli, right Kirti?  We will
feed Dabeli to Kirti because there is no such thing as Dabeli in the village.   The
best samosa chaat is available there
in the village.  So here we will feed him Dabeli.
Look guys, Papa has gone to get protein.
Look, Papa has brought all the protein
items.
Brought all the workout essentials.
Kavya is doing a very intense workout.  And
I also say yes.   You must be
seeing it, at least a little bit.  Isn't it
?
Yes.  Not just a few, a lot of changes are
visible.  You can look for Papa in old blogs
and also in the current blog.  Come on guys, look,
we have just reached
Can Place in our city.  From here
I have to get a cover for my mother.   I have to
buy a cover for Kirti and
also for Papa.  You should get it for Papa too, right?
Look, show me his phone.
Yes, come.  Look, its cover is also very damaged.  We will
cover this also.  Take this out and
keep it with you.  This
won't be a new yellow one, will it?
No, this is the crystal one.  Leather
silicone is the most popular right now.
See which one you like?  Look, which one was
like this all these days, so put silicone in
it or put transparent one first.   Take
this out and see which one looks good on
it because if it is plain then it might stick to it
[coughing sound].  Look,
Kirti's phone has become new.  It
looks so beautiful.  The cool color looks cool too.
What do you call these?
Pop socket.
Ok.  So we have to take this also.  It doesn't come out sticking like this.
Choose which one you want.  See which one you like and take it.
We bought too many things.  I bought all this for mom's phone cover.  Let's go
home now.  No, I will
eat something before going home.  Since we have come out, we must
eat something.  Papa, please keep this one.   No no, I still
look like that, no matter how much.   No matter
how it feels.  How true it is.
Yes.  Wow.   Hey, hold on.
Hey,
I am not taking it.  Guys, look, we have just
come down to eat Dabili.  We
will eat delicious hot Daabili.
Add a little less oil.
Look how nice it smells.  It
is hot too.   Take
this and hold it.
How are you feeling Vulture?  Feels very good.
I am eating it for the first time.  This is not found in the village.
This is not found in the village.
No.
So did you like this daabil or not?   Yes, I
liked it.
So we are feeding Kirti whatever is available in the village.
Guys, look, you do
n't have to buy diapers for Chiku baby.  So we have come to
wellness.  We will do some shopping here also.
We are not looking for ourselves.
Papa took some O Diet Cook.  Now we
see for ourselves.  Need something like face wash or something?
Look, Papa's fan.
Hi hello hello
I have been searching for you since so many days, do you know are you
searching for me, you
mean for class, I have come here for a
month,
okay, since then
I am also from Kolhapur,
oh wow, I have
come here from Kolhapur, thank you,
what are you looking for, I come here after roaming around, wait I am taking the
diet, I have taken the
diet, what else did you want to take,
wait I am looking, brother what do you want to take,
first take my pants,
yes take it, the child, what do you want, do you want chocolate,
take this one, this small one.  No one will eat something so big.
You are the only one who will eat it.   Shout out loud.
Speak quickly, quickly,
quickly.   He is feeling
so shy right there.
I heard that he was secretly
telling this to his mother.  She is Kavya didi.  Kavya
is Didi.
Yes.   Give a
second to Kavya didi.
I will eat ice cream.  I will go to Kashmir.
Look which one is ice cream?
This is needed in it.   Do
n't ask Kirti outside.  Which cup did you want to
eat, so I said don't eat anything in a cup, just take
a family pack, stuff yourself with 1/2
kg, take
half a kg,
which one do you want, tell me
take mango, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take mango, no,
he doesn't like mango, papa,
yes, take whatever you like, take
chocolate or vanilla, take
chocolate,
chocolate, yes, take the box, take this one,
okay, take this, no problem,
take whatever you want, if you want
those beans,
yes, keep it,
I can eat it alone,
oh come on, eat the whole box alone.
Look, Guys just came to get diapers.  I am
taking so many things home.  Come on,
let's go straight home now.  Now I will not roam anywhere.   Guys,
we have reached home.  Look, everyone is sitting
here after eating food.  We have just finished eating.
We are sitting and resting.
What is this?  This is going on its own.
Protein Protein.
This dad has brought all these goals again.
Look Kirti, how beautiful she has become after coming here.
Exactly the same
aunty is saying, aunty and I, both of us are getting
dark by staying at home, aunty and
I and didi, look [laughs] how fair we have become, we have become
very fair, it is looking very good here, the
skin is
glowing a lot,
one two three, hi guys,
welcome back to my channel, it is fun, so guys, right now
we are going to admit our bhabhi
in the hospital, the delivery is going to happen today or
tomorrow and the little baby will be
in our hands, so bhaiya and bhabhi are coming right now.  I am
bringing some stuff from home and
then we will go straight to the hospital.
Would you like to say something, Grandma?  You are going to become a grandmother and I am
waiting for our child to be born.
And he is going to be a grandfather.
I will become grandfather and you will become aunt.  She will also become an
aunt.
Younger aunt, elder aunt.
So guys,
Bhabhi's delivery is going to take place in the same hospital where Chiku baby was born.
Now I don't know whether it will be a normal delivery
or a caesarean.  Now we have
no idea.  Now we will go to the hospital and whatever the
doctor says will happen.
[laughter]
[laughter] Guys,
we've arrived, and the
hospital was in front, not behind.  Mom was going this way,
so we all were laughing at her.  Come on, come.
We reached before the patient.
Arrived an hour early.  An hour ago.
Doctor, he's going to yell at him too.   Do
n't you understand why I come so late?  It
's good that he should be scolded.
Both couples should be scolded.   You
know, when Chiku was being born,
Papa and I were sitting here early in the
morning.
We were just sitting there with our faces like this [music].  And I was wondering
when the baby would come?  When will the baby come?
What was the point of going inside?
No, everyone will get scolded a lot.   I am going to get
scolded.  Who all came?  Brother and
sister-in-law have come,
brother and sister-in-law will come
and your mother has not come, has she come?
Yes, then someone is needed, everyone has come inside,
yes they have come, go, you all go and get
scolded,
we are waiting, go, go, you also
go and get scolded,
yes
I will sit here,
where is your brother, he is
parking the car,
my mother will also come, go, you only go,
which scolding to get, get
scolded by the doctor, go, go, go, go, go
and where is the child's father?   I am
coming, park the
car on the side.
Look brother,
all the best brother,
what will we both do?  I will sit and stay here.
Will clap.  Yes.
What happened, Papa?   The
doctor is doing the checkup right now.  I will tell you now
what to do.
Good.
Sit for a while now.  Have some patience.
Ok.   Things are
going like Caesar is going to happen.
Yes.
Hmm.
Ok.  Let's see what the doctor says.
What happened?  Got the room ready and took the same
room which belonged to Chiku.  I mean, on my time.   I took the
same room that was available during your time.  Yes.  Well,
as we move forward here,
old memories are coming to our mind.  I am
remembering everything from the time when Chiku baby was being born on Chiku.  Let's
go upstairs now.
Look at this.   There
is a camel here and this is what I am saying.   Are
you remembering everything from Chiku Baby's time
?
Yes, everything, Chiku used to live here on this bed
and I said
we are sitting there too,
I said no, there is silence everywhere, yes, from
today onwards I will keep silence everywhere,
here
Kirti kept more silence and did not say a word, she is going to
become aunt, she said she
needs neck, very good
neck, she needs
both, decide what you want,
yes Bhabhi, the one who will give it,
okay, this much will do,
first let it be decided, will Bhaiya give it or only then will I
say, okay, Bhaiya only will give it,
Bhaiya did not even ask once what do you
want [laughs]
Bhaiya I feel tensed,
Bhaiya you also ask [laughter] I am
sitting tensed, that is why I did not ask, I am
not hearing anything,
ears [sound of clearing throat] have also closed, hit me, you should have [ __ ] me
in childhood, you
missed that, you did
not [ __ ] me very early in childhood, guys,
checkup is going on inside and we are
waiting here.  Now we have to wait like this for five to six
hours when we don't know when
I will tell you when the delivery will take place?  The delivery
will take place at night,
we will come at night, whoever is your grandchild, whoever it is will
come at night, if it is
not done in the morning then it shines like the sun, at
night it shines like the moon,
today is 15th August,
see, it is a
good muhurta and it happened yesterday too, it is good, tomorrow is Teej,
Teej is Hariyali Teej,
today is tomorrow,
Teej is today, I have kept a fast,
not today, it is tomorrow, I told him, it is today,
I just saw guys, please give me tomorrow's fast,
everyone has kept a fast [laughs]
I have also kept a fast, so guys, our sister-in-law will
deliver today or tomorrow, whether it is a boy
or a girl, we are very happy for both of us.
All of you please pray for Bhabhi and
like this video.  Don't forget to subscribe to the channel.